Guide to the Lolo National Forest Collection 1894-1987
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana-Missoula
- Photographic Materials, 1894-1987; Series VI; 351 images
  - Remount Packers Field Day Contests, October 2-4, 1930; Haskins "cargoing." Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0126)
  - Remount Packers Field Day Contests, October 2-4, 1930; Major Kelley presenting 2nd prize to P.H. Thompson. Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0127)
  - Remount Packers Field Day Contests, October 2-4, 1930; Trying out the loads. Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0128)
  - Remount Packers Field Day Contests, October 2-4, 1930; General view. Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0129)
  - Remount Packers Field Day Contests, October 2-4, 1930; Packer Erlewine of Ninemile loading mule. Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0130)
  - Loading fire pack, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0131)
  - Remount Packers Field Day Contests, October 2-4, 1930; Major Kelley presenting 3rd prize to Leonard Bush of the Kaniksu. Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0132)
  - Remount Packers Field Day Contests, October 2-4, 1930; Guy Woodworth of Coeur d'Alene National Forest, winner of 1st prize (Box 19, Photo number 87-0133)
  - Remount Packers Field Day Contests, October 2-4, 1930; St. Joe landing for fire. Selway in the background. Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0134)
  - Remount Packers Field Day Contests, October 2-4, 1930; Workman of Kootenai "cargoing." Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0135)
  - Remount Packers Field Day Contests, October 2-4, 1930; McCormick of the Bitterroot "cargoing." Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0136)
  - Loading pack mules at Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0137)
  - Remount Packers Field Day Contests, October 2-4, 1930; Clearwater loading for fire-field day. Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0138)
  - Cargoing packs at Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0139)
  - Packing mules, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0140)
  - Ninemile mules along Flathead Road, 1939; Photo by Lew Nichols (Box 19, Photo number 87-0141)
  - Spring shoeing at Camp McDonald Basin, May 7, 1939; Photo by Lew Nichols (Box 19, Photo number 87-0142)
  - Virgil Pears at Cascade American Sadler, circa 1939; Photo by Lew Nichols (Box 19, Photo number 87-0143)
  - Pack string, circa 1934-1942; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0144)
  - Packing mules, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0145)
  - Pack string at Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0146)
  - Pack string at Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0147)
  - Hauling lumber for ready cut buildings into backcountry, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0148)
  - Packer Days at Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0149)
  - Packer Days at Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0150)
  - Loading Forest Service equipment, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0151)
  - Loading Forest Service equipment, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0152)
  - Fire crew and pack stock, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0153)
  - Stock truck and pack stock, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0154)
  - Decker pack saddle, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0155)
  - Two horses and stock truck, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0156)
  - Mules and fire equipment, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0157)
  - Stock truck and mules, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0158)
  - Stretchers at Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0159)
  - Stretchers at Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1934-1942; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0160)
  - Fire figthers and equipment, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0161)
  - Fire figthers and equipment, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0162)
  - Phillips pack saddle used by the US Army circa 1924, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0163)
  - Phillips pack saddle used by the US Army circa 1924, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0164)
  - Loading mules with prefabricated building materials, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0165)
  - Loading mules with prefabricated building materials, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0166)
  - Pack string on the trail, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0167)
  - Pack string on the trail, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0168)
  - "Beauty" the mule, circa 1934-1942; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0169)
  - Decker pack saddle, "O.P. Robinett", circa 1934-1942; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0170)
  - Mule and a bed, circa 1934-1942; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0171)
  - Packer Days at Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1934-1942; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0172)
  - Packer Days at Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0173)
  - Manty up a load, February 3, 1938; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0174)
  - Mule with Decker saddle, February 3, 1938; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0175)
  - Mule being shod while in a shoeing stall, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0176)
  - Group at Ninemile Remount Depot, 1938; Elers Koch (Yale alum), Walt Graves (founding dean of Yale Forest School), Myra Wolf (Yale alum), Gifford Pinchot (Pennsylvania Governor), and Major Evan Kelley (Regional Forester). Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0177)
  - Loading mules, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0178)
  - Wrangler loading mule, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0179)
  - Pine Street USFS warehouse, circa 1925; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0180)
  - Packing emergency rations at warehouse on West Front Street in Missoula, Montana, circa 1927-1928; Marlin, Al Johnson, Rassmussen, Leo Abel, and Lloyd Noel. Photo courtesy of Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0181)
  - Front Street warehouse, circa 1920s-1930s; Gus Peterson. Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0182)
  - Pine Street warehouse, circa 1920s-1930s; Leo Abel and Art Kramis. Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0183)
  - Pine Street warehouse, circa 1920s-1930s; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0184)
  - Fire equipment warehouse in Missoula, Montana, 1920; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0185)
  - Jack Clack and his pack in Missoula National Forest with special equipment, 1925; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0186)
  - Roll #6 card, undated; Most of the photos on the original USFS roll attributed to K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0187)
  - Unloading trucks for the Civilian Conservation Corps in Missoula, Montana, August 1, 1933; Photo by C.P. Fickes (Box 19, Photo number 87-0188)
  - Headquarters of CCC camps near Ninemile Remount Depot, November 7, 1933; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0189)
  - CCC boys digging irrigation ditch for Ninemile Remount Depot pastures, November 7, 1933; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0190)
  - Temporary CCC camp at Ninemile Remount Depot, October 4, 1933; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0191)
  - Dismantling Packers' Meadow at CCC camp, August 1933; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0192)
  - Building barracks Ninemile CCC camp, August 1933; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0193)
  - CCC digging irrigation ditch at Ninemile Remount Depot pastures, 1933; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0194)
  - CCC headquarters near Ninemile Remount Depot, November 7, 1933; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0195)
  - CCC camps near Ninemile Remount Depot, 1933; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0196)
  - Making foundation for barracks at Ninemile CCC camps, October 1933; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0197)
  - CCC men resting during barracks construction at Ninemile camp, October 1933; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0198)
  - Bulletin board at Ninemile CCC temporary camp, October 4, 1933; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0199)
  - Washing up at the Ninemile CCC camp, October 4, 1933; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0200)
  - CCC boys resting up after lunch, March 1934; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0201)
  - Ninemile CCC camp, 1933; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0202)
  - Ninemile CCC camp, 1933; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0203)
  - CCC boys digging irrigation ditch, November 7, 1933; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0204)
  - Building Ninemile CCC camp, October 1933; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0205)
  - Shop at Ninemile CCC camp, 1933; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0205)
  - CCC boys planting Ponderosa Pine on Ellis Creek, 1939; Logged-off area acquired by exchange. Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0206)
  - CCC boys planting Ponderosa Pine on Ellis Creek, 1939; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0207)
  - Ponderosa Pine planting job, May 1938; R1 technique; tree has been placed in the hole. Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0208)
  - Ponderosa Pine planting job, circa 1938-1939; Boy giving final tamping with blade. Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0209)
  - Ponderosa Pine planting job, circa 1938-1939; Pressing tree in with blade of tool. Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0210)
  - CCC planting crew at lunch, May 1939; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0211)
  - CCC boys planting Ponderosa Pine on Ellis Creek, May 1939; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0212)
  - CCC tree planter on Ellis Creek near Huson, Montana, circa 1938-1939; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0213)
  - CCC tree planter, Butler Creek job, 1938; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0214)
  - Method planting Ponderosa Pine seedlings, May 1939; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0215)
  - Method planting Ponderosa Pine seedlings, May 1939; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0216)
  - CCC boys planting Ponderosa Pine on Ellis Creek, May 1939; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0217)
  - CCC boys planting Ponderosa Pine on Ellis Creek, May 1939; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0218)
  - CCC boys planting Ponderosa Pine on Ellis Creek, May 1939; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0219)
  - Distributing seedlings at noon, May 1939; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0220)
  - Men filling bags with tree seedlings, May 1939; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0221)
  - Roll #7 card Ninemile Historic Photos, circa 1894-1920; Original USFS roll. Ninemile Historic photos: Early Days in the Ninemile Valley (Box 19, Photo number 87-0222)
  - Ninemile house, 1894 (Box 19, Photo number 87-0223)
  - JE Breen, Ninemile First Ranger, 1906 (Box 19, Photo number 87-0224)
  - First post office in Martina, Montana, 1908 (Box 19, Photo number 87-0225)
  - Paddy McElligott Martina residence and post office, undated; Closed in 1918 (Box 19, Photo number 87-0226)
  - Anconda Copper Mining Company camp 4 at Stoney Creek behind Ninemile, 1918 (Box 19, Photo number 87-0227)
  - Martina, Montana, 1919 (Box 19, Photo number 87-0228)
  - Donkey engine at Ninemile, circa 1920; Possible locations: Butler, Stark, or Kennedy (Box 19, Photo number 87-0229)
  - Lima-Shay gear locomotive in Ninemile area, circa 1920; "100 Spot" Pat McElligott (engineer) (Box 19, Photo number 87-0230)
  - Miners at Marion Creek in Ninemile area, circa 1900; Billy Sparks, Jim Kelley, and Bill Henry (Box 19, Photo number 87-0231)
  - Martina, Montana, 1919 (Box 19, Photo number 87-0232)
  - Ninemile House, circa 1919; Charlie Proebstal with a Model T (Box 19, Photo number 87-0233)
  - Logging camp between old school and Ninemile house, 1894 (Box 19, Photo number 87-0234)
  - Ninemile, 1894 (Box 19, Photo number 87-0235)
  - Roll card, July 10, 1987; "Ninemile Ranger District Collection used in '32 Years in the Mule Business'" (Box 19, Photo number 87-0236)
  - Ninemile Remount Depot under construction, circa 1930s (Box 19, Photo number 87-0237)
  - Overview of Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1930s (Box 19, Photo number 87-0238)
  - Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1930s (Box 19, Photo number 87-0239)
  - Ninemile Remout Depot support cottage, circa 1934-1942 (Box 19, Photo number 87-0240)
  - Ninemile Remout Depot support cottage, circa 1934-1942 (Box 19, Photo number 87-0241)
  - Ninemile Remout Depot support cottage, circa 1934-1942 (Box 19, Photo number 87-0242)
  - Ninemile Remout Depot support cottage showing garage door, circa 1934-1942 (Box 19, Photo number 87-0243)
  - Overview of Ninemile Remount Depot showing original entrance, September 1936; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0244)
  - Ninemile CCC camp entrance, circa 1934-1942 (Box 19, Photo number 87-0245)
  - CCC boys resting during construction of barracks at Ninemile Remount Depot, October 1933; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0246)
  - Ninemile Remount Depot barn and mules, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0247)
  - Aerial view of CCC Ninemile camp, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0248)
  - Two CCC boys packing, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0249)
  - CCC boys and equipment, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0250)
  - CCC boy operating radio, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0251)
  - Ninemile Remount Depot mule string, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0252)
  - Packers and mules at Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0253)
  - Packer and two mules at Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0254)
  - Two CCC boys packing radio, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0255)
  - Fire tower lookout at Ninemile, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0256)
  - Packer and two mules, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0257)
  - Trucks loaded with pack mules at Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0258)
  - Trucks at Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0259)
  - Loaded Forest Service truck, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0260)
  - Loaded Forest Service truck, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0261)
  - Ninemile Remount Depot from old entrance, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0262)
  - Loading mules at Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0263)
  - Ninemile Remount Depot mule stock, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0264)
  - Ninemile Remount Depot mule stock, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0265)
  - Packers at Ninemile Remout Depot, Winter Range Road, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0266)
  - Overview of Winter Range Road near Perma, Montana, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0267)
  - Winter Range Road near Perma, Montana, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0268)
  - Winter Range Road near Perma, Montana, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0269)
  - Residence in Ninemile area, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0270)
  - Loading mules, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0271)
  - Mules at Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0272)
  - Forest Service truck loaded with mules on road, circa 1934-1942 (Box 19, Photo number 87-0273)
  - Trucks loaded with mule strings at Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1934-1942 (Box 19, Photo number 87-0274)
  - Trucks and mules at Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1934-1942 (Box 19, Photo number 87-0275)
  - Truck and mules next to Ninemile Remount barn, circa 1934-1942 (Box 19, Photo number 87-0276)
  - Ninemile Remount Depot from old entrance, circa 1934-1942 (Box 19, Photo number 87-0277)
  - Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1934-1942 (Box 19, Photo number 87-0278)
  - Ninemile Remount Days, circa 1930s (Box 19, Photo number 87-0279)
  - Residence in Ninemile area, circa 1934-1942 (Box 19, Photo number 87-0280)
  - Trail crew from the Ninemile Remount Depot crossing a creek with a pack string in tow, undated; Photo courtesy of Tom Reese (Box 19, Photo number 94-4683)
  - On trail, undated; Photo courtesy of Tom Reese (Box 19, Photo number 94-4684)
  - On trail, undated; Photo courtesy of Tom Reese (Box 19, Photo number 94-4685)
  - Trail crew, undated; Photo courtesy of Tom Reese (Box 19, Photo number 94-4686)
  - Ninemile Remount Depot, undated; Photo courtesy of Daniel Longpre (Box 19, Photo number 94-4687)
  - Ninemile Remount Depot in winter, undated; Photo courtesy of Daniel Longpre (Box 19, Photo number 94-4688)
  - A buffalo, undated; Photo courtesy of Daniel Longpre (Box 19, Photo number 94-4689)
  - Logging in winter at Ninemile, January 1937; "Stumps must be low. 30" of snow, 22 degrees below." (Box 19, Photo number 94-4690)
  - Logging in winter at Ninemile, January 1937; "Pole and jack stand" (Box 19, Photo number 94-4691)
  - Logging in winter at Ninemile, January 1937; "Paul's sled" (Box 19, Photo number 94-4692)
  - Packstring, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4692a)
  - Men and horses on ferry, undated; Flat-top ferry with people and a horse on it and canoe alongside, possibly on the Clark Fork River (Box 19, Photo number 94-4693)
  - Loaded packstring from Ninemile Remount Depot, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4694)
  - Loaded packstring from Ninemile Remount Depot, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4695)
  - Packstring, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4696)
  - CCC crew clearing land at Ninemile, circa 1934; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 94-4697)
  - CCC crew clearing land at Ninemile, circa 1934; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 94-4698)
  - CCC crew clearing land at Ninemile, circa 1934; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 94-4699)
  - CCC crew clearing land at Ninemile, circa 1934; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 94-4700)
  - CCC crew clearing land at Ninemile, circa 1934; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 94-4701)
  - CCC crew clearing land at Ninemile, circa 1934; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 94-4702)
  - CCC crew building fences, circa 1934; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 94-4703)
  - CCC crew building fences, circa 1934; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 94-4704)
  - CCC crew building fences, circa 1934; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 94-4705)
  - CCC crew building fences, circa 1934; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 94-4706)
  - CCC crew building fences, circa 1934; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 94-4707)
  - CCC crew building fences, circa 1934; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 94-4708)
  - CCC crew building fences, circa 1934; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 94-4709)
  - CCC crew building fences, circa 1934; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 94-4710)
  - Mules in Ninemile Remount Depot pasture, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4711)
  - Mules and horses in Ninemile Remount Depot pasture, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4712)
  - Mules and horses in Ninemile Remount Depot pasture, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4713)
  - Mules and horses in Ninemile Remount Depot pasture, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4714)
  - Mules and horses in Ninemile Remount Depot pasture, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4715)
  - Mules and horses in Ninemile Remount Depot pasture, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4716)
  - Mules and horses in Ninemile Remount Depot pasture, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4717)
  - Mules in Ninemile Remount Depot pasture, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4718)
  - Mules and horses in Ninemile Remount Depot pasture, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4719)
  - Mules and horses in Ninemile Remount Depot pasture, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4720)
  - Mules and horses in Ninemile Remount Depot pasture, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4721)
  - Mules and horses in Ninemile Remount Depot pasture, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4722)
  - Mules and horses in Ninemile Remount Depot pasture, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4723)
  - Mules and horses in Ninemile Remount Depot pasture, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4724)
  - Mules and horses in Ninemile Remount Depot pasture, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4725)
  - CCC crew building fences, circa 1934; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 94-4726)
  - CCC crew planting Ponderosa Pine along Butler Creek in the Lolo National Forest, 1938; The CCC also helped build miles of truck trails in the region. Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 94-4727)
  - Fire company out of Ninemile Remount Depot, 1933 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4728)
  - Henry Alexis of Butte, Montana and CCC Camp Company 953, circa 1930s (Box 19, Photo number 94-4729)
  - Snipe hunting at Ninemile CCC camp, circa 1930s (Box 19, Photo number 94-4730)
  - Cooks preparing Christmas dinner for CCC Company 952, circa 1935-1937 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4731)
  - Improvised mess hall, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4732)
  - CCC crew loading for trip to project at Ninemile camp, 1934 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4733)
  - CCC crew loading for trip to project at Ninemile camp, 1934 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4734)
  - CCC crew returning to Ninemile camp from work, circa 1930s; Laundry and shower building on right (Box 19, Photo number 94-4735)
  - Ninemile CCC project constructing dam on Butler Creek (Company 952), circa 1930s; Photo courtesy of Bill Perusich (Box 19, Photo number 94-4736)
  - The stallion "Grand Menard" at Ninemile Remount Station, undated; The second Ninemile CCC cmap was named "Grand Menard" and later became a smokejumper base. (Box 19, Photo number 94-4737)
  - The Forestry project office at Ninemile CCC camp, circa 1933-1934; Dispatch location board. Winter operation with three companies on hand: Company 939 - summer at Coram, Montana; Company 1962 - at Whitetail camp in Ashland, Montana; Company 952 - summer at Deep Creek in Darby, Montana. Photo courtesy of Bob Croskrey (Box 19, Photo number 94-4738)
  - Early day mess hall of Company 952, undated (Box 19, Photo number 94-4739)
  - Ninemile CCC camp, circa 1934-1936; Photo courtesy of Bob Croskrey (Box 19, Photo number 94-4740)
  - The Forestry project office at Ninemile CCC camp, circa 1934-1936; Same as 94-4738 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4741)
  - A winter scene at the Ninemile CCC camp, circa 1934-1936 (Box 19, Photo number 94-4742)
  - A winter scene at the Ninemile CCC camp #3, circa 1935-1936; Taken from project distpath area: mess hall on far left, barracks 1 and 2. Photo courtesy of Bob Croskrey (Box 19, Photo number 94-4743)